[{"answer": "I understand.  No, I'm not", "docId": "Strange-Days.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "That's right", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Me bailing your sorry pale ass out of jail twice in the last six months", "docId": "Strange-Days.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Define love", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "Strange-Days.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Commissioner my friend", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "No, see a friend is more than one person constantly doing favors for another.  You just suck people along with your schemes and your scams and your slick act.  Well I'm out.  I got a kid, I got rent, I got an e", "docId": "Strange-Days.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "No, you're just trying to get off", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Shoulda told me about your new gig, buddy", "docId": "Strange-Days.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "You should feel like shit", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "He knows what he's doing.  He's worn before... a lot", "docId": "Strange-Days.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "It gives me... I don't know... maybe two hundred people who I know wear", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "See, it's all about what they see walking in.  A dead hooker, handcuffs, penetration... they'll see a trick gone wrong.  Random kill.  The kind you never solve", "docId": "Strange-Days.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "No it doesn't", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "I can't tell you.  You've got to see", "docId": "Strange-Days.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Mace.  I know what you think about the wire.  But I'm asking you to do this.  It's that important", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "We got to make another copy of this. Little life insurance", "docId": "Strange-Days.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": " I've got a good idea, yeah", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "So, let's see, I've got Tran's goons, some squidhead psycho and the that place all trying to kill me.  Happy new year, my friend", "docId": "Strange-Days.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "There's a plus side", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Okay, we gotta get over there.  Can you borrow a dress from my friend or somethin", "docId": "Strange-Days.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Whatya mean?  We're going!  my friend's gonna do her right there unles", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "I guess", "docId": "Strange-Days.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "No.  It didn't", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Take it to him", "docId": "Strange-Days.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "No.  Trust me", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Well...  Get going.  You're still bleeding", "docId": "Strange-Days.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Yeah.  See you there", "qsentId": 28}]